Viewers there are many of you in a mess
in terms of business and finances.
With God all things are possible!
Be revived!
Your finances be revived!
Your business be revived!
Your career be revived!
Your destiny be revived!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Confess your freedom right now.
Confess your freedom.
Begin to confess your freedom.
Hallelujah, confess your freedom
Glory, power.
Your confession matters. Without your confession,
we cannot place you.
We cannot place you without your confession.
I am free! I am blessed!
I am cured! I am healed!
Yes, we cannot place you without your confession,
your confession matter.
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
Confess in the presence of God.
Remember our message today.
When a farmer gets his seed into the ground,
he does not dig it up
every day to see how it is doing
but believes it is aright.
Believe that it is settled.
Tell your neighbor, I believe that my case is settled.
I can't hear you, face your neighbor. I believe that my case is settled.
I believe that my business is settled.
I believe that my finances are settled.
Begin to believe right now.
Believe, believe!
My case is settled!
My finances are settled!
My health is settled!
My career is settled!
I believe, I believe, I believe ...in the name of Jesus.
My case is settled in Heaven!
In heaven
It is settled
Tell your neighbor...tell your neighbor, my business is settled in Heaven
I believe!
I believe...you should believe that your case is settled.
You should believe not your case is settled!
Believe now that your finances are settled!
I believe! Begin to confess your belief, right now.
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
In Jesus Christ name we pray!
Remember our message today,
it is a very vital issue for you.
When you get home sit down
Once you place your seed
into the soil and cover it,
you do not go back to check to see whether it is doing well
You believe that it is settled.
Tell your neighbor, "I believe that my case is settled!
I believe that my finances are settled!
I believe my health is settled!
It is well with my soul!
It is well with my body!
It is well with my finances!
I say it is well with my fiancees!
My business, it is well. It is a new dawn!
I say, "Good morning to you
my finances!"
I say, "Good morning to you my health!"
I say, "Good morning to you,
my finances, it is done!"
Hallelujah
Yes, if you believe this message about the farmer,
that once they put their seed in the soil, they don't go back there.
to dig it up and see how it is doing.
In the same vein,
if they could believe in nature,
why not believe in the God of nature?
Why not believe in the God of nature?
Why not believe in his imperishable seed?
The word of God says, "It is well!"
Prophet T.B. Joshua: Tell your neighbor
Congregation: It is well
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
Hallelujah
Can you hear what the word of God says?
If the farmer says, it is well to their seed they buried in the soil,
they never go there to dig it up to see how it is doing.
But they say, it is settled!
Say, my case is settled!
Do you hear what the word of God says?
The word of God say, "let the weak say, I am strong!"
Let the poor say, " I am blessed!"
Let the sick say, " I am healed!"
Confess!
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
Hallelujah.
I want to send a signal to your spirit.
The message today is very powerful.
It will really revive everyone
I want to remind you
Everyone of us were once farmers, at least 90%
Even if you go back to the village now, your father is a farmer.
If you go back to the village and you spend (3) days, you will likely go to the farm (1) day.
If i am talking to you let me see your hand.
Once again if you go the village just to visit and you spend (5) days. You will likely go to farm 2 days out of
5 days. You want to go to see where you grew up when you were very small.
You are setting a trap catching cats. Catch...catch
You still want to see it.
We are all farmers.
Back to help your faith
In those days, remember when you put your seed into the ground or soil and burry it, when you put your seed
you did not go back there again to see how it was doing.
You said, "it is well!" Till today, that is the principle of farming.
If they could believe so much in nature,
why not believe in the imperishable seed,
which is the word of God.
The word of God says, "let the weak say I am strong."
Let the sick say, "I am healed!"
Let the poor say, "I am blessed!"
I can't hear you, " I am blessed"
The prisoner say, "I am free!"
Confess it right now!
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
You don't need to wait, and see the prison open.
Tell your neighbor, " I don't need to wait to see my body healed...I am healed."
I don't need to wait to see my money being paid.
My money has been paid!
Confess it right now!
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
You don't need to wait until you see your career
flourish. My career is flourishing!
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
That should be your confession.
You don't need to wait and see your body
healed. I am healed already.
That is faith. Faith is expecting God to do,
what he promised to do!
What does He promise to do?
To: heal, bless, and promote you.
Tell your neighbor, I don't need to wait to see my body being healed. I am healed!
I don't need to wait to see my business flourish, my business is flourished already!
In the same vein, farmers
do not wait to see their seed grow.
They believe, it is growing!
That is their belief.
Farmers do not wait to see their seeds grow.
They believe that it is growing, it is settled.
THE SCOAN SUNDAY MASS PRAYER
So the problem that you are facing now is that you are waiting to see your body healed
When the man of God say, "you are healed!"
You now say, "Am I healed?" That is where satan waits.
This is where obstacles comes, when you don't apply faith..you can't receive!
Tell your neighbor...if you don't apply faith..you can't receive!
When the man of God says, "you are healed...by faith I am healed!"
When the man of God talks to you by faith..you receive it by faith.
Tell your neighbor, when the man of God talks to you by faith..you receive it by faith.
When the man of God says you are healed! Receive it by faith.
Faith!
The issue of farmers applicable to everyone in Christian life.
Simple. When a farmer
puts his seed into the soil,
he does not go back there to see how
it is doing, he says, "thank you Lord."
No matter the weather, condition, or season,
they believe it is settled.
Forever, oh Lord
Your word is settled
In heaven, it is settled
Forever, oh Lord
Your word is settled
In heaven, it is settled
Forever, oh Lord
Your word is settled
In heaven, it is settled
Forever, oh Lord
Your word is settled
In heaven, it is settled
That is, your case is settled!
Your business is settled!
Your finances are settled!
Someone is somewhere
settling your business!
Someone is busy settling your finances!
Tell your neighbor, someone is somewhere settling my business
Someone is busy settling my career!
Someone is buys settling my business!
Someone is buys settling my finances!
YES!!!!!!!!
Hallelujah! Thank you.
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony
Engage with God.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies from SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV...changing lives, chaining nations, and changing the world.